All right. If you are a real estate
agent and you are stuck at 500 to a,000
followers or you are stuck in 200 to 500
view jail, this episode is for you
because we are going to build out the
2026 content playbook for real estate
agents. And there is no better person to
do it than my guest right here. We have
the Alyssa Stalker who is the head of
education and what was the second part
of the title?
>> Strategy.
>> The head of education and strategy at
Coffee and Contracts. It sounds like
it's almost like a political position
like you should be in the cabinet of the
White House or something.
>> I know.
>> Like you're the head of the department
of education. This is Alyssa Socker.
She's also the host of the Above Asking
podcast which I have been on. Phenomenal
podcast. If you are interested in
content, real estate, anything along the
lines of social media, how to produce
content to help you get more followers,
leads, go check out the Above Asking
podcast. Alyssa, I am thankful and
honored for you to join us. How you
doing?
>> I'm good. Thanks for having me. Excited
to be back.
>> Yes, welcome back. It was fun doing your
pod. Today, we're going to do something
a little bit different. We're going to
just build out the 2026 content
blueprint for real estate agents. And we
are here in August. So it's really the
second half of the year. What worked the
first six months is probably not going
to work the next six months.
>> Absolutely.
>> A lot a lot has changed. The algorithm
changes on a daily basis. Content
strategy, wherever attention is
constantly keeps changing. So let's get
straight into it.
>> Yeah.
>> I'm an agent. I'm listening to this
podcast right now and I'm pissed because
I am stuck at a certain number. I am
just posting non-stop. I'm getting zero
engagement. I'm getting no leads. Let's
build out a content playbook for this
agent. What is the first thing that you
would do if you're an agent and you just
have no idea kind of what direction to
go in with your content? What's the
first thing that you would do?
>> Well, first I want to tell this person
to take a deep breath and realize that
this happens to everybody so they're not
alone. Uh not to feel bad about it
because it's just data. A lot of the
times people stay stuck with low views,
low engagement because they keep
repeating the same things and they're
not learning from what they're posting,
which is actually the definition of
insanity. So, I would take a step back,
zoom out a little bit from what you've
been doing, try to see if there's
anything that you can look at to
potentially determine if there's an
outlier in your content. like out of all
those flatline views and engagement
posts, are there any that stood out that
had anything that took off? What are the
attributes about them? That could be a
leading indicator of a starting point.
Um, but most of the time, it's not it's
it's not a consistency problem for a lot
of agents when they're actually actively
trying to post, but they're not seeing
results. oftentimes is that they really
aren't speaking to anyone specific. And
I think what we've learned from this
first half of the year in 2026, now more
than ever, and people have said this for
years, but now more than ever, it's so
important to niche down because of how
Instagram specifically is categorizing
and displaying content to people.
>> Yes. So, I want to touch upon both of
those. First, the outlier content.
That's I've never like obviously we've
talked about outlier content before but
I've never heard that's a great place to
start and that's the best place to
start. So great tip right there. What we
mean by outlier content as Alyssa says
is go through your last six months of
posts, see what performed the best and
then figure out why it performed the
best. For me, I'll just use myself as an
example. I want to say early part of the
year, I posted a video saying AI won't
replace real estate agents, but agents
who use AI will replace those who don't.
And I was making fun of all the people
that pontificate on real estate panels
and say that because everybody says
that. And that post got like 800
comments, right? And it's by far the
most like follows I've gotten all year
from a post. That line has been used now
like as a joke in all of my comments
moving forward. So, I've basically used
that outlier content, separated that
from the rest of the memes and decided,
okay, I need to go kind of allin or at
least like change up my strategy where
I'm kind of 70% more talking head yap
style where I'm voicing a very specific
heavy opinion about content or about
what people are talking about in real
estate.
>> Yeah.
>> So, that is and I've done it just
because I saw, hey, that did really
well. Let's do it again. Right.
>> Yeah. and it's it's it's done really
well for um my content. So, I'd highly
recommend others. And then when you say
being very specific with an avatar or
being very specific with like your
niche, how can an agent find their
niche? Like how how does an agent know
where exactly they should be what target
audience they should be
>> uh reaching out to?
>> Yeah, I think it starts like with your
own personal brand. Like who are you?
What do you represent? Um, what do you
want people to know about you? Who do
you immediately connect with? A lot of
people think of an ideal client as like
a demographic or a particular stage of
home ownership like a upsizer and, you
know, or a downsizer or, you know,
things like that. And I think those are
too broad really. I think you need to
think about who the person is that
you're talking to. And the best way I
can say this is that a lot of the
content that I'm seeing perform well
right now on Instagram is in fact very
casual. Like it's actually becoming very
fun and playful out there. Like we're
seeing just even in like the typography
like everyone's using butter yellow
basic fonts, right? And they're just
getting one point across. They're trying
to say one message to one person. Um,
there's a lot of content like that that
I'm seeing, especially like since
carousel posts are performing really
well across the board for a lot of
people. I know for me they perform
better than reals um, by far. Um, but
also like single image posts are back.
So when you when you dial back like the
messaging of okay, I want to get out
this entire point in a post where I've
previously either had a talking head
reel explain a point or I have done, you
know, seven slides in a carousel to get
this whole message across. If we dial
that back to going back to like what can
I fit in one slide, like one single
image post and a caption, that's almost
how you can reverse engineer who you're
speaking to because you kind of got to
fit everything into this one spot like
if you're making that type of a post.
And so when you are looking at
developing content, like you want to put
your own personal filter, your own
personal lens on it, but also think
about what about this relates to like
who I'm trying to reach. So, if you're
trying to talk about, you know, three
city name pieces of lore that no one
ever knew, um, for people who have kids
or something like that, like it could be
you want to frame it up for like what it
is that you're talking about, who it's
for, but then add your lens to it, too.
So, I think if you can I just told you
to zoom out, but maybe now zoom back in
of like who exactly you're trying to
speak to. Um, and and well, we were
zooming out on your content problem.
Now, we're zooming in on niching down.
But if you could think about who it is
that you really really connect with,
like is it people who are in early
stages of parenting? Is it dog parents?
Is it uh professionals who are
relocating because there's a big hub for
a new company? Like think about who
these people are, what stages of life
they're at. Where are they eating? Where
are they hanging out? Like what are
their interests? Are they playing pickle
ball on a Friday and joining a social
club or are they somebody who loves to
couch rot on the weekend and have, you
know, a beautiful living room all to
themselves? Like you think about these
things really specifically. And it
sounds counterintuitive because real
estate agents especially right now are
like, I just want business. Like just
give me business. Like I'll work with
anybody. Um, but I think in order to get
to that level where you start to have
people just automatically calling you
because they they like you, they connect
with you, they hear about you, you have
to start with one person to get to that
point.
>> At the very beginning of what you just
said, you mentioned what do you want
people to know about you.
>> Yeah. And I think that's kind of rare
rarely said at least I you know we've
never said that on on this show, but I'm
trying to I'm just going to use personal
examples here. I'm not trying to talk
about myself, but it is you know it's
all relevant what I'm going to say here.
>> Um I want people to know more about me,
hence the background, right? There's
Star Wars, there's USC, there's baseball
cards, there's books I've never read,
there's the book I wrote, there's more
Star Wars, there's Yankee. like all this
stuff is about me right behind me
because it has a deeper connection with
people with my content.
>> Yeah.
>> I'm also trying to do that where I work
in the fact that, you know, we just had
a baby or I like sports in my Instagram
stories. I always like add something at
the end of a statement in my broadcast
channel about some bet that I'm placing,
right? These kind of like little hints
of my personality that make people
connect with the brand on a deeper
level. So that's the personal lens that
you're mentioning. Yeah, that
>> real estate agents should not be afraid
to work into their content,
>> right? It's it's it's not what does the
audience want to see, but also what does
the audience need to know about me in
order to like me, trust me, and then
work with me.
>> Yeah, absolutely. And it's not just
about like knowing your interests or
putting out interests you think that
they have the same ones of. It's just
sharing enough of yourself to where
people feel like they get to know you.
And if they feel like they know things
about you, they feel automatically
connected and like they trust you.
>> Yes, absolutely. Okay, so let's get into
some of these casual posts because I
totally agree that Instagram is becoming
a little bit more fun where Loi content
is performing really well. Three years
ago was the highly edited kind of
Hermosi style where you had to pay
someone to do captions. You no longer
have to do that. You can do that in Cap
Cut, in Instagram reels, with the edits
app. So, like all these tools are kind
of at your service. Now,
>> if you are that agent and you were stuck
at the 500 followers, is there like a
first piece of content after you've kind
of looked at your previous content that
you would start to make? Like, is it
B-roll style? Is it carousels? What
would that be?
>> Yeah, I would actually try I would AB
test both because I've seen some people
do really well with local B-roll. And I
would say the the best the best piece of
content a real estate agent can play
around with that always resonates is
local content. I think what you're what
you are solving for is how to frame that
local content through that that ideal
client personal brands personal brand
lens that we just talked about. But I
think local content is always relevant.
It always performs. It's what real
estate agents are most reluctant to
post. Like I hear them grumble and gripe
about it because they say, "I I sell
real estate. I want to talk about my
business." But we all know um and it's
been said on this show, I'm sure, a
million times, people just don't come to
Instagram to look at real estate 247.
So, I think if you can play around with
local content, try B-roll footage with a
really strong text hook. Um, one of the
one of the biggest downfalls I see with
agents posting content is they could
have a beautiful B-roll, a nicely
designed carousel, they could be using a
coffee and contracts template and it
looks great, but they haven't adjusted
the hook so that it actually creates
that right framing or they don't know
how to hook at all. I actually just
developed a hook an interactive hook
generator for the podcast and um it's
been great because it's sol it's so many
people have been telling me like this is
the one unlock that I've needed because
I just suck at hooks like I don't know
how to create a hook um with what I'm
trying to say. So most of the times
people lead with three things to do this
weekend in city name and that's very
broad. So, when we talk about like
niching down, you know, three things to
do this weekend in city name that you've
probably never heard of, especially if
you're a mom of two. Um, so you've added
additional context and framing of who
this is for. And what the byproduct of
that is that the way Instagram
categorizes content now with the
algorithm, it's like I could be looking
up one thing one time on my phone now or
on Instagram and now that for the next
24 hours it's testing similar type of
content in front of me based on what I
looked up and it's or it's it's heard me
talk about something and that's all I'm
seeing. So it's really an even playing
field to get in front of people. So the
more specific you are, the more likely
now you are to land in front of the
right people. You don't have to fight
for those views as hard where so you
don't need to worry about like being so
broad. So I whether the format doesn't
matter. I would test B-roll reels. I
would test carousels, even single post
images. Just make sure you're trying it
out with something interesting with
local content that is specific to who
you want to reach and has your personal
point of view, your take or your framing
or who you are attached to it.
>> So, that's so good for the hook framing.
And if you see me looking over here,
it's because I'm writing notes down and
and and noting to Haley when a good clip
is and that hook part was the good clip.
Sometimes I like just letting the
audience know how the brain is thinking
as the podcasts are going as I'm sure
you do with above asking where you hear
someone say something you're like that
was the clip right there. So that was
the clip right there on the hooks. If
you get anything out of this episode
it's how to make more specific hooks. So
throw this video a like right now if you
got value out of that. Make sure you're
subscribed to the channel. So with these
hooks like that it's so good to instead
of say the three best things to do this
weekend in Spokane. the three best
things to do this weekend in Spokane if
you're a mom with kids under five.
>> Yeah.
>> And what you said what you said there is
you think that your TAM your total
addressable market will be bigger if you
just keep it broad and you say the three
best things to do in Spokane. But that
is so broad that no one actually cares
about that. But like you said, it's
going to land in the algorithm of those
moms by saying that. I've seen this guy.
Have you heard of Gabe Einhorn?
>> I don't think so.
>> This guy just popped up on my feed. I
don't even know how I followed. I don't
think I followed him, but somehow I did.
And he's basically non-stop in my feed.
He uses hooks that are so specific.
Well, he'll say something like,
>> "If you're watching this video on August
15th or 16th,
>> uh, you're going to have amazing luck."
Like, it's such a cheap way to kind of
game the algorithm, but then it makes
you it gives you that kind of like icky
feeling of, damn, the algorithm is like
serving something very specific to me
because I am watching it on August 13th.
>> Yeah.
>> It's like when you're scrolling TikTok.
I'm a new dad and that it says if you're
a dad with an 11week baby who was just
crying through the night all night, it's
just like, do they have a camera in my
room or something? How is this possible?
>> But it's that specific content that then
hits those people. Let's take a quick
break to tell you about our next
in-person event in Scottsdale, Arizona,
September 22nd through the 23rd. BAM
camp team leaders. This is not a
conference. You will not sit in the back
of some freezing ballroom listening to
keynote after keynote with eight hours
of notes that you will never look at
again. This is a working session for
team leaders looking to scale past a h
100red million. If you want to recruit
and retain top agents, if you want to
convert more leads without spending more
on marketing, if you want to build a
referral and repeat business that
compounds over time, compounds over
time, Bam Team Leaders is for you. Gino
Buffari, Byron Lazine, Luke Ari from
Reminder Media, Tom Tulle, George Lton,
Lisa Chinati. Our lineup is insane. So,
grab your tickets. The link is down in
the description to Bam Camp team
leaders. Can't wait to see you guys in
Scottsdale.
>> Absolutely. I'm noticing that now more
than ever. And I've noticed that with my
own content, just like you were talking
about, you noticed an outlier, you kept
doubling down on that. And what worked
for you? What works for me are these
repeatable carousels. I started posting
them probably like a year and a half
ago. And every time they would
outperform anything else I would post.
So over time this year I started to
realize nobody comes to my account for
tips anymore. Like that's not what
they're nobody wants my tips. But uh
they follow along my content because
they actually feel seen. So I I make
these carousels for real estate agents
just seeing them where they're at in
their business. And I get very specific
of things that like they're going
through, they're dealing with. And my
following has my following was stagnant
last year. Like I I have like a micro
following compared to a lot of you. But
I was at like 10,000 followers all of
last year and then this year like I'm
almost up to 15. So I've almost grown
half my following in a year. Um, but
that's because I found a piece of
content that works for me and I just
kept running with it. And it's bringing
in the beauty of it is not just growing
the followers, growing the reach, and
getting engagement. It's bringing the
right people to me that I can connect
with. And that's the best thing ever
because anything else I post in my
stories or I have now I have a podcast
episode I share, they immediately
resonate with that because they're the
right audience. So, it's interesting how
certain types of content um are so
specific, but they will continue to
serve you over time because they're just
bringing the right people that are going
to care about everything else you have
to say.
>> So, you're meeting people kind of in
their content journey with your content.
>> Absolutely. What's an example of one of
those carousels? Like a a hook, I guess,
that that reaches
>> Well, you know,
>> is it like if you're an agent who's
stuck in 500 view jail, for example,
don't worry.
>> No, a lot of the times a lot of the
times I'm not even necessarily calling
out like their content painoint. Like
the last one I just did was, "It's crazy
what an I found you on Instagram can do
for my mental health as a real estate
agent." Um, so immediately that's
connecting with somebody who
>> wants to grow on Instagram. They like
love seeing that message come through
their inbox. Like they live for that.
That's the type of people I want
following me. Another one that I just
posted that did really well is people
only post their wins on social. So here
are some of my recent flops. It's kind
of like a polarizing thing against
myself. Like somebody wants to know, oh,
someone else struggled with struggles
with content too. And so I'm just
brutally honest, like literally one
person wanted my lead magnet the day
before that [clears throat] I posted.
Um, which is kind of sad and but
unusual, but I it happens, you know what
I mean? Um, so I do a lot of a lot of
posts like that. Self-care as a realtor,
and it's just me remembering I don't
have to earn my rest. Um, so I just I
try to I try to just help people feel
seen. Um, I think a lot of people are
always yelling at real estate agents
about what to do, what they're doing
wrong, um, and how to fix it. And I want
people to feel comfort, um, or laughter
or yap when they come to my account, um,
as a space where like they feel like
they can grow without pressure. Um,
they're going to get like no BS advice.
Um, maybe unasked, but [laughter] but,
uh, most of the time it's just to make
people feel connected to me. So, I think
as a real estate agent, the best thing
you can do is help people feel connected
to you and how you're connected to the
community or their specific circle
within your community.
>> I'm trying to think how to flip that. If
you're an agent and you're trying to
reach specific clients to make them feel
comfortable where it's like, you know,
if you if you're 35 and haven't bought a
house yet, do not worry. Like most
people most people haven't. Like, are
there ways to do that?
>> Yeah. So, like even that one post, that
self-care post that you just put up,
like self-care as someone in their
mid30s who's yet to buy a house. And
then you can talk about things that they
can do to like take care of their
mindset, take care of themselves, like
start the process. Like, it's all about
hooking people in a way that makes them
feel like, oh, self, wait, self-care as
a person who hasn't done this yet. Like,
that's me. Okay, I'll keep swiping. And
you might be offering something funny at
first, something cheeky, something
supportive. Um, but then in the end
you're offering them a solution by
saying, "Don't worry, you're not
behind." Like lots of people are like
that and guess what? That's exactly who
I help. Um, and that's going to
immediately convert or connect them to
you.
>> Yeah. That does so much better than kind
of FOMO or rent shaming or like you have
to do this now before school starts.
Like that sort of content doesn't really
work. Yeah.
>> It's really just oh, I want to feel low
pressure with this person.
>> Yeah. I want to
>> there's actually term for it. It's
called being a comfort creator. Um and
so I've [clears throat] kind of taken
that angle for myself um for a long time
and it's it's for about like the past
year and it's worked really well for me.
I actually it makes my content more fun.
I enjoy creating what I create um
because it's authentic to me and I know
it's I know it's helping someone. I'm
not just trying to create transactional
content where I'm selling something or
offering something. It's it's really
about it's connection content versus
transactional content.
>> Can you pull up Ricky Kuth's page,
Haley? Because I think Do you follow
him, Melissa?
>> I do, but I can't say I've seen his
content in a minute.
>> Okay. Well, you just said the word
comfort content, and I really think this
is kind of what Ricky's doing. Okay. And
I've heard like some people have shared
this. So just go to his like all black
create mode post. So yeah, click that
one. If your real estate agent, if your
real estate agent is still answering the
phone at 9:00 p.m. on Saturday, you
don't have an agent. You have someone
who cares about your family's future.
This thing has 11,000 likes, right?
That's kind of comfort content for
agents. Keep keep going to more create
mode
posts like this. Here's another one. A
real estate agent's confidence is an
arrogance. It's the result of surveying
every market cycle and still being here.
>> Yeah.
>> So, this is very
nice content for agents to share. Uh,
real estate agents wake up knowing they
have zero guaranteed income, but they
show up anyway. That's called courage.
12,000 likes.
>> This content is crushing.
>> Yeah,
>> some people have sent me this con
content and been like, what's the point
of this? But now that you say it's
comfort content, that does make sense
because it's just kind of like, hey,
this is really easy for an agent to
share and kind of feel like, hey, at
least someone kind of sees me. Yeah, it
is hard not knowing that I have this
guaranteed income. Another thing I want
to say about that content is it's create
mode,
>> all black background text only. So that
kind of touches upon your original point
too of like loweffort content where
sometimes if you have an idea, just one
thing, tweet it out, screenshot it, and
then post it.
>> Yeah, absolutely. Um, and I I think the
cool part about that content, like for
me and what what's working for Ricky
right there, is that I'm sharing that
content for the agent, but I put it
through the lens of the agent. I'm no
longer a real estate agent, but all my
content is framed as though I am. And I
think about this with everything that I
post. I think would a real estate agent
want to share this to their stories or
repost this so that their potential
clients see it and it would make them
look good. Um, so I always think about
that like the reason my content gets
shared a lot by other agents is because
I'm actually helping positioning them or
something they'd love their clients to
know about them or how hard they work or
what they're going through and that they
feel good about sharing it. So that's
another thing to think about with your
content is is this something someone
would want to share. And there's a lot
of ways real estate agents could create
that same content that you just showed
from Ricky for potential buyers and
sellers or locals in their area by just
meeting them where they're at,
describing the feeling, and helping them
connect with it.
>> Yeah. The like rethinking your content
to what is the action someone's going to
take with this? Are they going to share
this in in the DMs? Are are they going
to share this to their story? Are they
going to comment on it? or is this just
blasting them with information where
they're going to have no engagement
necessary with it?
>> Yeah.
>> And a lot of agents still kind of fall
back in that chat GPT script firsttime
buyer education or I'm going to tell you
about the housing market and give you
five different statistics that no one
really cares about that people are
confused about. So, another thing you
mentioned at the very beginning of the
episode was focusing on one specific
thing for each piece of content. Yeah,
>> we're starting to do that more with like
I have a viral agent newsletter. It's
just one tip. The whole point of this
show, even though we're kind of going in
different directions, is one topic.
That's why the walkthrough, which is
great, which you've been on, but you
know, Jason became the chief marketing
officer of Real, so co-host down. I
figured with this, it's more let me just
go deep dive on one topic and not have
three different things. Just like at a
conference when you're kind of inundated
with so many different speakers and you
know you go from sales to marketing to
sales to AI, you're utterly confused.
That's how people consuming content are.
>> So if you're thinking about your videos
or your posts or your emails, what's one
thing that I could say right here?
>> And if I could say that in 20 30
seconds, it's usually a little bit more
effective.
>> Absolutely. And something else to keep
in mind is we we love to see a healthy
content mix for real estate agents at
Coffin Contracts. like our content
strategy is built around mostly local
content, listing content because you got
to show what it is that you sell. Um,
and then a little bit of authority
building content and that's the smallest
percentage. And what that is is talking
about like case studies, um, positioning
yourself as a real estate agent, what
makes you stand out. That's actually the
smallest part of the content strategy.
So, if you can think about everything
that you post, it's like mostly for them
with a little bit about you. Um, but you
don't have to have such a vast array of
content. Like there's a lot of creators
out there that post a lot of the same
style post over and over and over again
and it works for them. So, it's it's
really about seeing what's going to work
for you, what your goals are. If you
want to grow if you want to grow your
account, local content is probably going
to be the fastest way to attract new
followers and grow your account. If you
want to convert more business and get
more leads, listing content is probably
going to help you out with that. Um, the
authority building content does help
build trust. It helps nurture, but
you're not going to get, you have to
manage expectations that every post has
a different goal. You're not going to
get a ton of likes on authoritybuilding
nurture style content like you are on a
local sharable where you share like a
contrarian take on your city and it's
going to go local viral because
everybody's like, "Oh my god, that's
hilarious." Like totally agree with
that. Like they're sending it to their
friends. Like that that's that's the
difference between like you have to
understand the goal of each post and
what the expectation is or the outcome
should be.
>> Yeah. I think a lot of people do get
kind of tied to the engagement and the
result of the post. The authority
building, meaning like if you're on the
real trends list, right? Or say you hit
a sales goal, that sort of stuff still
is important. There's a ton of agents
that just only do that content and
that's when it looks ridiculous.
>> If it's just like, "Hey, look at me.
Look at me. Look at me. Here's a new
listing. Here's a new award. Here's a
new, you know, goal that I have
achieved." That becomes nauseating. But
you do need to pepper these in once
every month or something like that so
that people
>> just know they're not going to engage
with it, but know that they saw,
>> oh, Alyssa Stalker, Alyssa Kernut,
whatever they Alyssa Kernut is listed
top five agents in Spokane. That's cool.
>> Yeah.
>> You know, like I I have to mention
Alyssa Kernut every single episode
still. I threw her in. Um, but yeah,
like that stuff does matter and no one's
going to share that post, but people
will just it it hits them in their head
where they understand that this agent
achieved a certain award or same with
reviews, which is kind of authority
building content, right?
>> Yeah. But I think there's a way that you
can take that kind of content and tell a
story with it, like turn it into a
carousel, turn it into framing this
specific client scenario as something
relatable to the next person that you
want to help. So, you're showing how you
showed up. You you you ultimately helped
them win the deal or achieve this
result. Um, and it establishes authority
without being as like braggy or boring
about it. But it's okay to brag on
yourself. And you should.
>> Yeah, you should. And another way you
could do it too, say you got on some
list your top five, whatever in your
area, you could green screen that
article or you could kind of make it
look like a news-based announcement so
it doesn't look like one of these kind
of AI graphics and then tell a story
about what you did differently to get
there. That's kind of more agent to
agent, but that's also a cool almost
self- testimonial of, hey, I got my
license 5 years ago. I am now on the
real trends list and I'm doing it
because I do this, this, and this. and
like here's what separates myself from
other agents. Like explaining it as
opposed to just posting it saying look
at me is such a better reframe.
>> Right. Right. You want to know how I got
on this list? Well, let me tell you.
>> Yeah. Exactly. So, yeah, that that's
really good. So, reviews.
Um I see a lot of agents that will just
kind of post in their stories or will
post like a screenshot of a review of,
you know, Zillow, Google review and it
looks awful. Do you have any
recommendation for agents to post
testimonials? Yeah, I think I if I was
still an agent, and I wish I did this
when I was, I'd ask my clients like,
"Can we do a little video? Like, can we
do a FaceTime style video, um, like
there's so many fun things you can do
where like you can give them a little
mic and you can film them and just ask
questions and have them answer and you
can string that together for a great
little reel." Like, there's so many so
many different ways. And I understand
you want them to do a written review. It
definitely helps with, you know,
rankings as far as showing up on some of
those sites. Um, when people are
searching for an agent, um, or people
just researching you and and getting
that credibility. But I think I think
there's some fun ways you can turn that
into content. You can take one line out
of the review, like make find the hook
line, make that the hook of a post, and
then break down the story of the
transaction and why they said that about
you. Um, there's there's a lot of
different fun ways rather than just
screenshotting the review. I think I
think when I see a review like that come
at me and I'm not actually looking to
hire someone in the moment like they're
posting it and it's maybe showing up in
my stories, I'm probably not even going
to read it because I can just tell this
is a review about someone and I'm not
looking to even hire anybody. So, it's
swipe. It's irrelevant to me. So, I
think if you want people to actually see
and remember that content, you got to
repackage it into like a a normal style
post to where they're they're thinking
they're seeing other content, but it's
really you sharing the context of a
review.
>> I just thought of a a good post idea for
that. So, you know how we do like
breaking news headlines on BAM or a lot
of agents will almost create like a
media story about themselves? Like, do
you know who Tatiana Lendano is?
>> No. you. I say no to everyone you
[laughter] ask me.
>> She's a big She's a big agent on social.
We had her on the over ask podcast back
in the day. Not the Above Ask, but the
over ask podcast. And it was Matt
Leonetti and I and she always does posts
where it says like millionaire real
estate agent gives her three social
media tips or something like that. So,
it's almost like you do a breaking news
style of yourself and you could say
something along the lines of, "You won't
believe what this client said about me
or you won't believe what this client
said about her agent." And then it's
kind of like this shocking face kind of
breaking news and then it swipes to the
actual thing, right? Just like it's just
another way to frame it where you're not
just publishing the testimonials. Also,
little trick of the trade is anytime
that you're trying to get a testimonial,
if you want to do the videos that you
were talking about, do it when they're
happy at closing time.
>> Yeah.
>> Right. Like do it when you're handing
them the keys. Do it when you just sold
their house for 10% over ask. Like you
can't really ask for a review
mid-transaction or after a couple weeks
has gone by. You kind of got to like hit
them in that moment where they're they
have the excitement of everything going
on.
>> Yeah, absolutely. And that's the best
time like you just bring out your phone
while on closing day you're giving them
the keys and say hey really quick I want
to I want to do a quick video and then
you just pull out your phone and ask
some questions and then you can clip
together whatever it is that they say.
You know
>> there's a fun reel going around right
now that I saw some people doing. I was
at Tom Ferry last week and I saw a
couple people do this style reel from
that and I was at in San Diego the week
before agents were doing this where it
was um I think I think Katie Day did
this too um where it was like you ask a
question and they answer but you ask
them actually something different and
then you like the funny question with
the answer. That's like a fun idea. Like
if you if that's your type of content,
like if you're funny and you're fun and
playful, that could be an idea that
could work for you.
>> Yeah, I that would actually be great for
a client testimonial where they're
saying something completely different
from what you asked. Okay, so that's the
content blueprint. Is there anything I
guess that kind of covers what agents
shouldn't be posting. Is there anything
for the second half of 2026 that agents
should just completely avoid that
they've maybe been doing the last couple
years?
>> Yeah, I would I would say mostly just
talking about your your self and your
listings too much in a boring way. That
just I still see it all the time. That's
not that's not a new take. We always say
like the just sold, just listed style
content. Um, your awards and just you
you basically have an entire billboard
about yourself when someone comes to
your your grid.
>> Um, I still see it all the time though.
I do profile audits every single week. I
do tons of them and I see it all the
time. I I can't say it loud enough. Get
an individual perspective on something.
Stand for something. have a lens or a
filter on something in your community.
Really find a way to stand out and post
things that people connect to and care
about. Local content is your your
easiest go-to just to begin with. Um,
start playing around. Um, and get really
good at hooking. Um, and I know you said
not what what not to do, but I always
love to follow up with what you should
do. So, I just want to reiterate, try to
practice hooks. Um, we have amazing
content in coffee and contracts. So, if
you want help with that, um, we create
templates for that. There's a lot of
resources out there. Otherwise, I know
you have resources. I have a hook guide
on above asking podcast. You can go to
the show notes of any episode of my
podcast and find resources. There's a
lot of free resources out there to learn
and get good at content. The only thing
to keep in mind is just be careful of
spreading yourself too thin, trying too
many different ideas. Try to narrow down
something to try, get data, try it for a
while, get data from it, learn from it,
and either pivot, try something else, or
double down on it if it's working.
>> One thing I didn't ask you about is AI
integration into any of this content. Is
there anything that you're doing with AI
to create better hooks or to create
better content? Yeah, I I would say um I
think that if you see an idea out there
you like, you can always ask uh AI to
help you reframe this hook for your
audience for your ideal client from your
point of view based on what it knows
about you or what you've told it about
your brand. If you haven't done that, I
would definitely set up your your AI
tool, whichever one you're using, to
learn about you, learn your brand. I
don't like AI written content. I don't
like AI generated content. I just saw a
post today um that Claude is now
watermarking content. Um we're seeing a
lot of AI generated tags start to to
come out. Um so I think there's going to
be a crackdown on that and people are
tired of it. They don't want to consume
it. People want real, which is why I
think this like kind of like loweffort
lowfi content is performing so well
because it's so easy. It's like it's not
even done by AI. It's obvious like
someone took a picture in their camera
roll and slapped some text on it.
>> Yeah, exactly. Have an opinion about
something.
>> Yeah.
>> Have your perspective.
>> Um I I I don't know if it's Neil Dinger
that says this, but he's been
emphasizing this at his forward
conference non-stop. Like people started
to follow him when he started to deliver
the news and then deliver his thoughts
on it.
>> Yeah.
>> Here's a restaurant. Here are my
thoughts on it. not just hear the top
three Italian places for dads between
the ages of 24 and 24 and a half who
like the Yankees, who have a dog, but
what do I actually think about it?
>> Because then you're providing your
unique perspective. Then you're giving
people a reason to follow you and like
you a little bit more because you're
sharing your opinions. You don't want to
just become someone that's just
reporting everything. We just had Katie
Day on. She kind of goes kind of more
that angle actually. So, she gave me a
good reason as to why you would want to
keep it more broad is like you're not
trying to alienate anybody, but she she
has her opinions in there for specific
articles. So, I think there's kind of
two routes to take with it.
>> Test it out, too. Like, if if you're
doing a top five list, you could have
your opinion in the captions.
>> Yeah, totally. And I don't think there's
a one-sizefits-all strategy for content.
>> That said, like my disclaimer is be
careful of listening to too many things.
because it can kind of create analysis
paralysis and you don't really form a
strategy when you're trying like five
different things at once, you know?
>> Yep. Okay. So, go back in all of your
posts if you're in 500 view jail. Look
at the outlier. Figure out what worked
with that. Make sure your hooks are a
little bit more specific. have an
opinion about something and have lowfi,
loweffort content, b-rolls, carousels,
and make sure that you are focused on
the three categories of listing content,
community content being the number one,
and an occasional
>> what was the other piece?
>> Authority building.
>> Authority content. Authority building.
There you go. And if you want to be
inundated with more information, you
have to check out the Above Asking
podcast with Alyssa Stalker. highly,
highly recommend it. Go follow the Alysa
Stalker. Some comfort content for you.
So, if you're an agent on your content
journey or you just want to feel a
little bit comforted, go follow her
account. Make sure you check out her
podcast. Make sure you like this podcast
and subscribe to the channel. We put out
videos like this every single week. It
really helps us in the algorithm. It's
by far the best way to show support.
Alyssa, I'm thinking 123 likes on this.
What do you think? [laughter]
>> Go specific with the number.
>> I 124. I I like the price is right
strategy.
>> 124 likes. If it hits that, something
crazy is going to happen. Thank you
everybody.
>> Okay, thanks.